Guide to the Rosalyn Baxandall and Linda Gordon Research Files on Women's Liberation TAM.210
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Women's Organizations: Florida (Gainesville; Jacksonville, FL), 1970s (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Women's Organizations: Jewish, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Women's Organizations: Maine (includes Freewoman's Herald), 1970s (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Women's Organizations: Massachusetts, circa 1970s (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Women's Organizations: Minneapolis, 1960s-1970s (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Women's Organizations: New Orleans, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Women's Organizations: New York City, 1968-1970s (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Women's Organizations: Older, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Women's Organizations: Religious, 1969-1976 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Women's Organizations: Religious, 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Women's Organizations: Religious: Newspaper Clippings, 1974, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Women's Page, the/ The Second Page (San Francisco, CA) (Newsletter), 1970-1975 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Women's Political Parties, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Women's Salon Press (New York, NY), 1976, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Women's Schools, 1969-1976 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Women's Studies: Discussions, Course Descriptions, 1969-1978 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Women's Time (Long Island, NY), 1975 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Women's Worker's Movement, History of, 1970-1974 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Work/ Labor, 1968-1977 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- WUNTRAC (satire), early 1970s (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Yale Non-Faculty Committee, circa 1972 (Box 7, Folder 42)